[
  {
    "question": "once",
    "answer": "una vez",
    "answerarray": [
      "una",
      "vez"
    ],
    "options": [
      "una",
      "vez"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "two times",
    "answer": "dos veces",
    "answerarray": [
      "dos",
      "veces"
    ],
    "options": [
      "dos",
      "veces"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m going to do it seven times.",
    "answer": "Voy a hacerlo siete veces.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "siete",
      "veces."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "siete",
      "veces."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to need the car three times tomorrow.",
    "answer": "Voy a necesitar el coche tres veces mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "necesitar",
      "el",
      "coche",
      "tres",
      "veces",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "necesitar",
      "el",
      "coche",
      "tres",
      "veces",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don’t understand why he wants to see it twice.",
    "answer": "No entiendo por qué quiere verlo dos veces.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "por",
      "qué",
      "quiere",
      "verlo",
      "dos",
      "veces."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "por",
      "qué",
      "quiere",
      "verlo",
      "dos",
      "veces."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "or",
    "answer": "o",
    "answerarray": [
      "o"
    ],
    "options": [
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it!",
    "answer": "¡Hazlo!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Hazlo!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Hazlo!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it five times.",
    "answer": "Hazlo cinco veces.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hazlo",
      "cinco",
      "veces."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hazlo",
      "cinco",
      "veces."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it six or seven times.",
    "answer": "Hazlo seis o siete vezes.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hazlo",
      "seis",
      "o",
      "siete",
      "vezes."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hazlo",
      "seis",
      "o",
      "siete",
      "vezes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It’s important to eat four or five times.",
    "answer": "Es importante comer cuatro o cinco veces.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Es",
      "importante",
      "comer",
      "cuatro",
      "o",
      "cinco",
      "veces."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Es",
      "importante",
      "comer",
      "cuatro",
      "o",
      "cinco",
      "veces."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "we",
    "answer": "nosotros/nosotras",
    "answerarray": [
      "nosotros/nosotras"
    ],
    "options": [
      "nosotros/nosotras"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We (females) are going out twice today.",
    "answer": "(Nosotras) salimos dos veces hoy.",
    "answerarray": [
      "(Nosotras)",
      "salimos",
      "dos",
      "veces",
      "hoy."
    ],
    "options": [
      "(Nosotras)",
      "salimos",
      "dos",
      "veces",
      "hoy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "how much?",
    "answer": "¿cuánto?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿cuánto?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿cuánto?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We want to know how much it is.",
    "answer": "Queremos saber cuánto es.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Queremos",
      "saber",
      "cuánto",
      "es."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Queremos",
      "saber",
      "cuánto",
      "es."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "how many?",
    "answer": "¿cuántos/as?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿cuántos/as?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿cuántos/as?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times?",
    "answer": "¿Cuántas veces?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times are we going to need it?",
    "answer": "¿Cuántas veces vamos a necesitarlo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "vamos",
      "a",
      "necesitarlo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "vamos",
      "a",
      "necesitarlo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times are you going to say it?",
    "answer": "¿Cuántas veces vas a decirlo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "vas",
      "a",
      "decirlo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "vas",
      "a",
      "decirlo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We don’t know how many times he can do it.",
    "answer": "No sabemos cuántas veces puede hacerlo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "sabemos",
      "cuántas",
      "veces",
      "puede",
      "hacerlo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "sabemos",
      "cuántas",
      "veces",
      "puede",
      "hacerlo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "only",
    "answer": "solo",
    "answerarray": [
      "solo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "solo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I only have…",
    "answer": "solo tengo…",
    "answerarray": [
      "solo",
      "tengo…"
    ],
    "options": [
      "solo",
      "tengo…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I only have three or four.",
    "answer": "Solo tengo tres o cuatro.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Solo",
      "tengo",
      "tres",
      "o",
      "cuatro."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Solo",
      "tengo",
      "tres",
      "o",
      "cuatro."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We only need to see it twice.",
    "answer": "Solo necesitamos verlo dos veces.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Solo",
      "necesitamos",
      "verlo",
      "dos",
      "veces."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Solo",
      "necesitamos",
      "verlo",
      "dos",
      "veces."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do I only have two chairs?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué solo tengo dos sillas?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "solo",
      "tengo",
      "dos",
      "sillas?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "solo",
      "tengo",
      "dos",
      "sillas?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do you only do it on Monday?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué solo lo haces el lunes?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "solo",
      "lo",
      "haces",
      "el",
      "lunes?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "solo",
      "lo",
      "haces",
      "el",
      "lunes?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why don’t you do it on Friday or Saturday?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué no lo haces el viernes o el sábado?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "haces",
      "el",
      "viernes",
      "o",
      "el",
      "sábado?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "haces",
      "el",
      "viernes",
      "o",
      "el",
      "sábado?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I only have the car on Monday and Tuesday.",
    "answer": "Solo tengo el coche el lunes y el martes.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Solo",
      "tengo",
      "el",
      "coche",
      "el",
      "lunes",
      "y",
      "el",
      "martes."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Solo",
      "tengo",
      "el",
      "coche",
      "el",
      "lunes",
      "y",
      "el",
      "martes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "first",
    "answer": "primero/a",
    "answerarray": [
      "primero/a"
    ],
    "options": [
      "primero/a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the first time",
    "answer": "la primera vez",
    "answerarray": [
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez"
    ],
    "options": [
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's the first time for me.",
    "answer": "Es la primera vez para mí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Es",
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Es",
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's not the first time for her.",
    "answer": "No es la primera vez para ella.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "es",
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez",
      "para",
      "ella."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "es",
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez",
      "para",
      "ella."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to think",
    "answer": "pensar",
    "answerarray": [
      "pensar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "pensar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I think that it’s the first time for you.",
    "answer": "Pienso que es la primera vez para ti.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Pienso",
      "que",
      "es",
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez",
      "para",
      "ti."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Pienso",
      "que",
      "es",
      "la",
      "primera",
      "vez",
      "para",
      "ti."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We think that she only does it on Friday.",
    "answer": "Pensamos que solo lo hace el viernes.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Pensamos",
      "que",
      "solo",
      "lo",
      "hace",
      "el",
      "viernes."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Pensamos",
      "que",
      "solo",
      "lo",
      "hace",
      "el",
      "viernes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "red",
    "answer": "rojo",
    "answerarray": [
      "rojo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "rojo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "blue",
    "answer": "azul",
    "answerarray": [
      "azul"
    ],
    "options": [
      "azul"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "green",
    "answer": "verde",
    "answerarray": [
      "verde"
    ],
    "options": [
      "verde"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "white",
    "answer": "blanco",
    "answerarray": [
      "blanco"
    ],
    "options": [
      "blanco"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "black",
    "answer": "negro",
    "answerarray": [
      "negro"
    ],
    "options": [
      "negro"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "yellow",
    "answer": "amarillo",
    "answerarray": [
      "amarillo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "amarillo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "orange",
    "answer": "naranja",
    "answerarray": [
      "naranja"
    ],
    "options": [
      "naranja"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "brown",
    "answer": "marrón",
    "answerarray": [
      "marrón"
    ],
    "options": [
      "marrón"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pink",
    "answer": "rosa",
    "answerarray": [
      "rosa"
    ],
    "options": [
      "rosa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the red chair",
    "answer": "la silla roja",
    "answerarray": [
      "la",
      "silla",
      "roja"
    ],
    "options": [
      "la",
      "silla",
      "roja"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the green table",
    "answer": "la mesa verde",
    "answerarray": [
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "verde"
    ],
    "options": [
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "verde"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the red car",
    "answer": "el coche rojo",
    "answerarray": [
      "el",
      "coche",
      "rojo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "el",
      "coche",
      "rojo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The red chair is on the green table.",
    "answer": "La silla roja está en la mesa verde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "La",
      "silla",
      "roja",
      "está",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "verde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "La",
      "silla",
      "roja",
      "está",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "verde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The black car is very fast.",
    "answer": "El coche negro es muy rápido.",
    "answerarray": [
      "El",
      "coche",
      "negro",
      "es",
      "muy",
      "rápido."
    ],
    "options": [
      "El",
      "coche",
      "negro",
      "es",
      "muy",
      "rápido."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I wouldn’t like to live in an orange house.",
    "answer": "No me gustaría vivir en una casa naranja.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "gustaría",
      "vivir",
      "en",
      "una",
      "casa",
      "naranja."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "gustaría",
      "vivir",
      "en",
      "una",
      "casa",
      "naranja."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Number six is yellow, but number eight is white.",
    "answer": "El número seis es amarillo, pero el número ocho es blanco.",
    "answerarray": [
      "El",
      "número",
      "seis",
      "es",
      "amarillo,",
      "pero",
      "el",
      "número",
      "ocho",
      "es",
      "blanco."
    ],
    "options": [
      "El",
      "número",
      "seis",
      "es",
      "amarillo,",
      "pero",
      "el",
      "número",
      "ocho",
      "es",
      "blanco."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Number four isn’t black, it’s blue and yellow.",
    "answer": "El número cuatro no es negro, es azul y amarillo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "El",
      "número",
      "cuatro",
      "no",
      "es",
      "negro,",
      "es",
      "azul",
      "y",
      "amarillo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "El",
      "número",
      "cuatro",
      "no",
      "es",
      "negro,",
      "es",
      "azul",
      "y",
      "amarillo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Buy the book!",
    "answer": "¡Compra el libro!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Compra",
      "el",
      "libro!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Compra",
      "el",
      "libro!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Call me later.",
    "answer": "Llámame más tarde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Llámame",
      "más",
      "tarde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Llámame",
      "más",
      "tarde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Give me the blue telephone.",
    "answer": "Dame el teléfono azul.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Dame",
      "el",
      "teléfono",
      "azul."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Dame",
      "el",
      "teléfono",
      "azul."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Come back with him.",
    "answer": "Vuelve con él.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vuelve",
      "con",
      "él."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vuelve",
      "con",
      "él."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lift up the black computer.",
    "answer": "Levanta el ordenador negro.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Levanta",
      "el",
      "ordenador",
      "negro."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Levanta",
      "el",
      "ordenador",
      "negro."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Speak more slowly, please.",
    "answer": "Habla más despacio, por favor.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Habla",
      "más",
      "despacio,",
      "por",
      "favor."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Habla",
      "más",
      "despacio,",
      "por",
      "favor."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it!",
    "answer": "¡Hazlo!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Hazlo!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Hazlo!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it with me, please.",
    "answer": "Hazlo conmigo, por favor.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hazlo",
      "conmigo,",
      "por",
      "favor."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hazlo",
      "conmigo,",
      "por",
      "favor."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "put it",
    "answer": "…ponlo…",
    "answerarray": [
      "…ponlo…"
    ],
    "options": [
      "…ponlo…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Put it on the red table.",
    "answer": "Ponlo en la mesa roja.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Ponlo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "roja."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Ponlo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "roja."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Put eight or nine beers on the table, please.",
    "answer": "Pon ocho o nueve cervezas en la mesa, por favor.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Pon",
      "ocho",
      "o",
      "nueve",
      "cervezas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa,",
      "por",
      "favor."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Pon",
      "ocho",
      "o",
      "nueve",
      "cervezas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa,",
      "por",
      "favor."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How’s it going? How are you?",
    "answer": "¿Qué tal?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "tal?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "tal?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello. How’s it going? Hola.",
    "answer": "¿Qué tal?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "tal?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "tal?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Very well. And you?",
    "answer": "Muy bien. ¿Y tú?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Muy",
      "bien.",
      "¿Y",
      "tú?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Muy",
      "bien.",
      "¿Y",
      "tú?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "how?",
    "answer": "¿cómo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿cómo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿cómo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's your name?",
    "answer": "¿Cómo te llamas?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "te",
      "llamas?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "te",
      "llamas?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "My name’s David.",
    "answer": "Me llamo David.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "llamo",
      "David."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "llamo",
      "David."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello. My name’s Jessica. What’s your name?",
    "answer": "Hola, me llamo Jessica. ¿Cómo te llamas?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hola,",
      "me",
      "llamo",
      "Jessica.",
      "¿Cómo",
      "te",
      "llamas?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hola,",
      "me",
      "llamo",
      "Jessica.",
      "¿Cómo",
      "te",
      "llamas?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's her name?",
    "answer": "¿Cómo se llama?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "se",
      "llama?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "se",
      "llama?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Her name is Marta.",
    "answer": "Se llama Marta.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Se",
      "llama",
      "Marta."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Se",
      "llama",
      "Marta."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's his name?",
    "answer": "¿Cómo se llama?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "se",
      "llama?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "se",
      "llama?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "His name is Juan.",
    "answer": "(Él) se llama Juan.",
    "answerarray": [
      "(Él)",
      "se",
      "llama",
      "Juan."
    ],
    "options": [
      "(Él)",
      "se",
      "llama",
      "Juan."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s happening/What’s going on?/What’s up?",
    "answer": "¿Qué pasa?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "pasa?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "pasa?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello Juan. How are you? What’s going on?",
    "answer": "Hola Juan. ¿Qué tal? ¿Qué pasa?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hola",
      "Juan.",
      "¿Qué",
      "tal?",
      "¿Qué",
      "pasa?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hola",
      "Juan.",
      "¿Qué",
      "tal?",
      "¿Qué",
      "pasa?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "He’s going to do it tonight.",
    "answer": "Va a hacerlo esta noche.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Va",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "esta",
      "noche."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Va",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "esta",
      "noche."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She’s going to know that we’re not here.",
    "answer": "Va a saber que no estamos aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Va",
      "a",
      "saber",
      "que",
      "no",
      "estamos",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Va",
      "a",
      "saber",
      "que",
      "no",
      "estamos",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to find",
    "answer": "encontrar",
    "answerarray": [
      "encontrar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "encontrar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She finds it very easy.",
    "answer": "Lo encuentra muy fácil.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "encuentra",
      "muy",
      "fácil."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "encuentra",
      "muy",
      "fácil."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I find it difficult.",
    "answer": "Lo encuentro difícil.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "encuentro",
      "difícil."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "encuentro",
      "difícil."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to find it today.",
    "answer": "Quiero encontrarlo hoy.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Quiero",
      "encontrarlo",
      "hoy."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Quiero",
      "encontrarlo",
      "hoy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you tell me where it is? …because I can’t find it.",
    "answer": "¿Puedes decirme dónde está? …porque no puedo encontrarlo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Puedes",
      "decirme",
      "dónde",
      "está?",
      "…porque",
      "no",
      "puedo",
      "encontrarlo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Puedes",
      "decirme",
      "dónde",
      "está?",
      "…porque",
      "no",
      "puedo",
      "encontrarlo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to sell",
    "answer": "vender",
    "answerarray": [
      "vender"
    ],
    "options": [
      "vender"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm selling the green car.",
    "answer": "Vendo el coche verde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vendo",
      "el",
      "coche",
      "verde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vendo",
      "el",
      "coche",
      "verde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why aren’t you selling the white one?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué no vendes el blanco?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "vendes",
      "el",
      "blanco?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "vendes",
      "el",
      "blanco?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm not selling it because I need it.",
    "answer": "No lo vendo porque lo necesito.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "vendo",
      "porque",
      "lo",
      "necesito."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "vendo",
      "porque",
      "lo",
      "necesito."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to sell it if he wants to buy it.",
    "answer": "Voy a venderlo si quiere comprarlo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "venderlo",
      "si",
      "quiere",
      "comprarlo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "venderlo",
      "si",
      "quiere",
      "comprarlo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you buy it if you don’t know how much it is?",
    "answer": "¿Cómo puedes comprarlo si no sabes cuánto es?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "puedes",
      "comprarlo",
      "si",
      "no",
      "sabes",
      "cuánto",
      "es?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cómo",
      "puedes",
      "comprarlo",
      "si",
      "no",
      "sabes",
      "cuánto",
      "es?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "money",
    "answer": "(el) dinero",
    "answerarray": [
      "(el)",
      "dinero"
    ],
    "options": [
      "(el)",
      "dinero"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a lot of",
    "answer": "mucho/mucha",
    "answerarray": [
      "mucho/mucha"
    ],
    "options": [
      "mucho/mucha"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "He has a lot of money.",
    "answer": "Tiene mucho dinero.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tiene",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tiene",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If I sell the house, I’m going to have a lot of money.",
    "answer": "Si vendo la casa, voy a tener mucho dinero.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Si",
      "vendo",
      "la",
      "casa,",
      "voy",
      "a",
      "tener",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Si",
      "vendo",
      "la",
      "casa,",
      "voy",
      "a",
      "tener",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a problem",
    "answer": "un problema (masculine)",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "problema",
      "(masculine)"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "problema",
      "(masculine)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The problem is that she has too much money.",
    "answer": "El problema es que tiene demasiado dinero",
    "answerarray": [
      "El",
      "problema",
      "es",
      "que",
      "tiene",
      "demasiado",
      "dinero"
    ],
    "options": [
      "El",
      "problema",
      "es",
      "que",
      "tiene",
      "demasiado",
      "dinero"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the bank",
    "answer": "el banco",
    "answerarray": [
      "el",
      "banco"
    ],
    "options": [
      "el",
      "banco"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to the",
    "answer": "a la",
    "answerarray": [
      "a",
      "la"
    ],
    "options": [
      "a",
      "la"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to the bank.",
    "answer": "Voy al banco.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "al",
      "banco."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "al",
      "banco."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to the house.",
    "answer": "Voy a la casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She has to go to the bank because she doesn’t have (any) money.",
    "answer": "Tiene que ir al banco porque no tiene dinero.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tiene",
      "que",
      "ir",
      "al",
      "banco",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "tiene",
      "dinero."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tiene",
      "que",
      "ir",
      "al",
      "banco",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "tiene",
      "dinero."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We are coming/going back to the hotel at six o’clock.",
    "answer": "Volvemos al hotel a las seis.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Volvemos",
      "al",
      "hotel",
      "a",
      "las",
      "seis."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Volvemos",
      "al",
      "hotel",
      "a",
      "las",
      "seis."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) need",
    "answer": "vosotros/as necesitáis",
    "answerarray": [
      "vosotros/as",
      "necesitáis"
    ],
    "options": [
      "vosotros/as",
      "necesitáis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "they need",
    "answer": "ellos/as necesitan",
    "answerarray": [
      "ellos/as",
      "necesitan"
    ],
    "options": [
      "ellos/as",
      "necesitan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You (plural) need a lot of money.",
    "answer": "Necesitáis mucho dinero.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Necesitáis",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Necesitáis",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They need a big car.",
    "answer": "Necesitan un coche grande.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Necesitan",
      "un",
      "coche",
      "grande."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Necesitan",
      "un",
      "coche",
      "grande."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time do you (plural) have dinner?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora cenáis?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "cenáis?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "cenáis?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We have dinner at nine o’clock.",
    "answer": "Cenamos a las nueve.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Cenamos",
      "a",
      "las",
      "nueve."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Cenamos",
      "a",
      "las",
      "nueve."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time do they arrive?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora llegan?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "llegan?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "llegan?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They arrive at eight o’clock.",
    "answer": "Llegan a las ocho.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Llegan",
      "a",
      "las",
      "ocho."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Llegan",
      "a",
      "las",
      "ocho."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) eat",
    "answer": "(vosotros/as) coméis",
    "answerarray": [
      "(vosotros/as)",
      "coméis"
    ],
    "options": [
      "(vosotros/as)",
      "coméis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "they eat",
    "answer": "(ellos/as) comen",
    "answerarray": [
      "(ellos/as)",
      "comen"
    ],
    "options": [
      "(ellos/as)",
      "comen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time do you (plural) have lunch?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora coméis?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "coméis?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "coméis?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We have lunch at one o’clock.",
    "answer": "Comemos a la una.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Comemos",
      "a",
      "la",
      "una."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Comemos",
      "a",
      "la",
      "una."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When do they have lunch?",
    "answer": "¿Cuándo comen?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "comen?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "comen?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They have lunch at two o’clock.",
    "answer": "(Ellos/as) comen a las dos.",
    "answerarray": [
      "(Ellos/as)",
      "comen",
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos."
    ],
    "options": [
      "(Ellos/as)",
      "comen",
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They sell cars.",
    "answer": "Venden coches",
    "answerarray": [
      "Venden",
      "coches"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Venden",
      "coches"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you (plural) selling the house?",
    "answer": "¿Vendéis la casa?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Vendéis",
      "la",
      "casa?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Vendéis",
      "la",
      "casa?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They don’t understand.",
    "answer": "No comprenden.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "comprenden."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "comprenden."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you (plural) understand?",
    "answer": "¿Comprendéis?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Comprendéis?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Comprendéis?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) live",
    "answer": "(vosotros/as) vivís",
    "answerarray": [
      "(vosotros/as)",
      "vivís"
    ],
    "options": [
      "(vosotros/as)",
      "vivís"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "they live",
    "answer": "(ellos/as) viven",
    "answerarray": [
      "(ellos/as)",
      "viven"
    ],
    "options": [
      "(ellos/as)",
      "viven"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They live in Madrid.",
    "answer": "Viven en Madrid.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Viven",
      "en",
      "Madrid."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Viven",
      "en",
      "Madrid."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you (plural) live in Spain?",
    "answer": "¿Vivís en España?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Vivís",
      "en",
      "España?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Vivís",
      "en",
      "España?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you (singular) want to go out with me?",
    "answer": "¿Quieres salir conmigo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Quieres",
      "salir",
      "conmigo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Quieres",
      "salir",
      "conmigo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are going out at ten o’clock.",
    "answer": "Salen a las diez.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Salen",
      "a",
      "las",
      "diez."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Salen",
      "a",
      "las",
      "diez."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "there is/are",
    "answer": "hay",
    "answerarray": [
      "hay"
    ],
    "options": [
      "hay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are three hotels here.",
    "answer": "Hay tres hoteles aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "tres",
      "hoteles",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "tres",
      "hoteles",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a woman in the room.",
    "answer": "Hay una mujer en la habitación.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "una",
      "mujer",
      "en",
      "la",
      "habitación."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "una",
      "mujer",
      "en",
      "la",
      "habitación."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a beer on the table?",
    "answer": "¿Hay una cerveza en la mesa?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "cerveza",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "cerveza",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a swimming pool",
    "answer": "una piscina",
    "answerarray": [
      "una",
      "piscina"
    ],
    "options": [
      "una",
      "piscina"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a swimming pool in the hotel?",
    "answer": "¿Hay una piscina en el hotel?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "piscina",
      "en",
      "el",
      "hotel?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "piscina",
      "en",
      "el",
      "hotel?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a lot of money in the car.",
    "answer": "Hay mucho dinero en el coche.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "mucho",
      "dinero",
      "en",
      "el",
      "coche."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "mucho",
      "dinero",
      "en",
      "el",
      "coche."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there (any) water in the swimming pool?",
    "answer": "¿Hay agua en la piscina?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "agua",
      "en",
      "la",
      "piscina?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "agua",
      "en",
      "la",
      "piscina?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a beach",
    "answer": "una playa",
    "answerarray": [
      "una",
      "playa"
    ],
    "options": [
      "una",
      "playa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a beach in Barcelona?",
    "answer": "¿Hay una playa en Barcelona?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "playa",
      "en",
      "Barcelona?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "playa",
      "en",
      "Barcelona?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There aren’t (any) beaches in Madrid.",
    "answer": "No hay playas en Madrid.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "playas",
      "en",
      "Madrid."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "playas",
      "en",
      "Madrid."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "of",
    "answer": "de",
    "answerarray": [
      "de"
    ],
    "options": [
      "de"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "David’s car (“the car of David”)",
    "answer": "el coche de David",
    "answerarray": [
      "el",
      "coche",
      "de",
      "David"
    ],
    "options": [
      "el",
      "coche",
      "de",
      "David"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maria’s car",
    "answer": "el coche de María",
    "answerarray": [
      "el",
      "coche",
      "de",
      "María"
    ],
    "options": [
      "el",
      "coche",
      "de",
      "María"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maria’s house",
    "answer": "la casa de María",
    "answerarray": [
      "la",
      "casa",
      "de",
      "María"
    ],
    "options": [
      "la",
      "casa",
      "de",
      "María"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I can't see Pablo’s computer.",
    "answer": "No puedo ver la computadora de Pablo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "puedo",
      "ver",
      "la",
      "computadora",
      "de",
      "Pablo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "puedo",
      "ver",
      "la",
      "computadora",
      "de",
      "Pablo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "near",
    "answer": "cerca de",
    "answerarray": [
      "cerca",
      "de"
    ],
    "options": [
      "cerca",
      "de"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I live near Barcelona.",
    "answer": "Vivo cerca de Barcelona.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vivo",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "Barcelona."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vivo",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "Barcelona."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you live near Córdoba?",
    "answer": "¿Vivís cerca de Córdoba?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Vivís",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "Córdoba?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Vivís",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "Córdoba?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They don't live near my house.",
    "answer": "No viven cerca de mi casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "viven",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "mi",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "viven",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "mi",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "near the",
    "answer": "de la...",
    "answerarray": [
      "de",
      "la..."
    ],
    "options": [
      "de",
      "la..."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "My house is near the bank.",
    "answer": "Mi casa está cerca del banco.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Mi",
      "casa",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "banco."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Mi",
      "casa",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "banco."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The pool is near the hotel.",
    "answer": "La piscina está cerca del hotel.",
    "answerarray": [
      "La",
      "piscina",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ],
    "options": [
      "La",
      "piscina",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The car is near the house.",
    "answer": "El carro está cerca de la casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "El",
      "carro",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "El",
      "carro",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "his/her",
    "answer": "su",
    "answerarray": [
      "su"
    ],
    "options": [
      "su"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Her car is near the house.",
    "answer": "Su coche está cerca de la casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Su",
      "coche",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "coche",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "His car is near Maria’s house.",
    "answer": "Su coche está cerca de la casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Su",
      "coche",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "coche",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a beach near the hotel?",
    "answer": "¿Hay una playa cerca del hotel?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "playa",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "una",
      "playa",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are selling the house near the beach.",
    "answer": "están vendiendo la casa cerca de la playa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "están",
      "vendiendo",
      "la",
      "casa",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "están",
      "vendiendo",
      "la",
      "casa",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Her house isn’t near the beach",
    "answer": "Su casa no está cerca de la playa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Su",
      "casa",
      "no",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "casa",
      "no",
      "está",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There’s a woman near the green car.",
    "answer": "Hay una mujer cerca del coche verde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "una",
      "mujer",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "coche",
      "verde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "una",
      "mujer",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "coche",
      "verde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I would like to live near the beach.",
    "answer": "Me gustaría vivir cerca de la playa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "gustaría",
      "vivir",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "gustaría",
      "vivir",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "more",
    "answer": "más",
    "answerarray": [
      "más"
    ],
    "options": [
      "más"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you speak more slowly, please?",
    "answer": "¿Puedes hablar mas despacio, por favor?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Puedes",
      "hablar",
      "mas",
      "despacio,",
      "por",
      "favor?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Puedes",
      "hablar",
      "mas",
      "despacio,",
      "por",
      "favor?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Her house is big, but my house is nearer (more near) the beach.",
    "answer": "Su casa es grande, pero mi casa esta más cerca de la playa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Su",
      "casa",
      "es",
      "grande,",
      "pero",
      "mi",
      "casa",
      "esta",
      "más",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "casa",
      "es",
      "grande,",
      "pero",
      "mi",
      "casa",
      "esta",
      "más",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to mean",
    "answer": "querer decir",
    "answerarray": [
      "querer",
      "decir"
    ],
    "options": [
      "querer",
      "decir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does “feliz” mean?",
    "answer": "¿Qué quiere decir “feliz”?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“feliz”?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“feliz”?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "“Feliz” means “happy”.",
    "answer": "“Feliz” quiere decir “happy”.",
    "answerarray": [
      "“Feliz”",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“happy”."
    ],
    "options": [
      "“Feliz”",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“happy”."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does “azul\" mean?",
    "answer": "¿Qué quiere decir “azul”?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“azul”?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“azul”?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you know what this means?",
    "answer": "¿Sabes lo que quiere decir esto?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Sabes",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "esto?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Sabes",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "esto?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "No, I don’t know what that means.",
    "answer": "No. No sé lo que quiere decir eso.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No.",
      "No",
      "sé",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "eso."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No.",
      "No",
      "sé",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "eso."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a word",
    "answer": "una palabra",
    "answerarray": [
      "una",
      "palabra"
    ],
    "options": [
      "una",
      "palabra"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are three words here that I don’t understand.",
    "answer": "Hay tres palabras aquí que no entiendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "tres",
      "palabras",
      "aquí",
      "que",
      "no",
      "entiendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "tres",
      "palabras",
      "aquí",
      "que",
      "no",
      "entiendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you know what this word means?",
    "answer": "¿Sabes lo que quiere decir esta palabra?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Sabes",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "esta",
      "palabra?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Sabes",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "esta",
      "palabra?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don’t know what that word means, but I know that it doesn’t mean “swimming pool”",
    "answer": "No sé lo que quiere decir esa palabra, pero sé que no quiere decir “piscina”.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "sé",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "esa",
      "palabra,",
      "pero",
      "sé",
      "que",
      "no",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“piscina”."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "sé",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "esa",
      "palabra,",
      "pero",
      "sé",
      "que",
      "no",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“piscina”."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "My name is Juan.",
    "answer": "Mi nombre es Juan.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Mi",
      "nombre",
      "es",
      "Juan."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Mi",
      "nombre",
      "es",
      "Juan."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Her name is Carolina.",
    "answer": "Su nombre es Carolina.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Su",
      "nombre",
      "es",
      "Carolina."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "nombre",
      "es",
      "Carolina."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "His name isn’t David. It’s Carlos.",
    "answer": "Su nombre no es David. Es Carlos.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Su",
      "nombre",
      "no",
      "es",
      "David.",
      "Es",
      "Carlos."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "nombre",
      "no",
      "es",
      "David.",
      "Es",
      "Carlos."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to write",
    "answer": "escribir",
    "answerarray": [
      "escribir"
    ],
    "options": [
      "escribir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to write your name.",
    "answer": "Voy a escribir tu nombre.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "escribir",
      "tu",
      "nombre."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "escribir",
      "tu",
      "nombre."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We’re going to write three words in the book.",
    "answer": "Vamos a escribir tres palabras en el libro.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "escribir",
      "tres",
      "palabras",
      "en",
      "el",
      "libro."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "escribir",
      "tres",
      "palabras",
      "en",
      "el",
      "libro."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Write it there, near your name.",
    "answer": "Escríbelo allí, cerca de tu nombre.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Escríbelo",
      "allí,",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "tu",
      "nombre."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Escríbelo",
      "allí,",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "tu",
      "nombre."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Write Maria’s name near your name.",
    "answer": "Escribe el nombre de Maria cerca de tu nombre.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Escribe",
      "el",
      "nombre",
      "de",
      "Maria",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "tu",
      "nombre."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Escribe",
      "el",
      "nombre",
      "de",
      "Maria",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "tu",
      "nombre."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They write it too small for me.",
    "answer": "Lo escriben demasiado pequeño para mí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "escriben",
      "demasiado",
      "pequeño",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "escriben",
      "demasiado",
      "pequeño",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "writing",
    "answer": "escribiendo",
    "answerarray": [
      "escribiendo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "escribiendo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm writing.",
    "answer": "Estoy escribiendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "escribiendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "escribiendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m doing it.",
    "answer": "Lo estoy haciendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "haciendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "haciendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you writing?",
    "answer": "¿Qué estas escribiendo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estas",
      "escribiendo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estas",
      "escribiendo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you eating?",
    "answer": "¿Qué estas comiendo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estas",
      "comiendo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estas",
      "comiendo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are they having lunch at four o’clock?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué están comiendo a las cuatro?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "están",
      "comiendo",
      "a",
      "las",
      "cuatro?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "están",
      "comiendo",
      "a",
      "las",
      "cuatro?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She's writing a book.",
    "answer": "Está escribiendo un libro.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Está",
      "escribiendo",
      "un",
      "libro."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Está",
      "escribiendo",
      "un",
      "libro."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I get up at seven o’clock.",
    "answer": "Me levanto a las siete.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "levanto",
      "a",
      "las",
      "siete."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "levanto",
      "a",
      "las",
      "siete."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to get up/to get oneself up",
    "answer": "levantarse",
    "answerarray": [
      "levantarse"
    ],
    "options": [
      "levantarse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to stay/remain",
    "answer": "quedarse",
    "answerarray": [
      "quedarse"
    ],
    "options": [
      "quedarse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m staying here tomorrow",
    "answer": "Me quedo aqui mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "quedo",
      "aqui",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "quedo",
      "aqui",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm not staying here.",
    "answer": "No me quedo aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "quedo",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "quedo",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re staying with me.",
    "answer": "Te quedas conmigo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Te",
      "quedas",
      "conmigo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Te",
      "quedas",
      "conmigo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to stay with you",
    "answer": "Quiero quedarme contigo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Quiero",
      "quedarme",
      "contigo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Quiero",
      "quedarme",
      "contigo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you want to stay with her?",
    "answer": "Quieres quedarte con ella?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Quieres",
      "quedarte",
      "con",
      "ella?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Quieres",
      "quedarte",
      "con",
      "ella?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She doesn’t want to stay here",
    "answer": "No quiere quedarse aquí",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "quiere",
      "quedarse",
      "aquí"
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "quiere",
      "quedarse",
      "aquí"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ourselves (reflexive form)",
    "answer": "nos",
    "answerarray": [
      "nos"
    ],
    "options": [
      "nos"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We get up at 6 o’clock",
    "answer": "Nos levantamos a las seis.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Nos",
      "levantamos",
      "a",
      "las",
      "seis."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Nos",
      "levantamos",
      "a",
      "las",
      "seis."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We have to get up soon.",
    "answer": "Tenemos que levantarnos pronto.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tenemos",
      "que",
      "levantarnos",
      "pronto."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tenemos",
      "que",
      "levantarnos",
      "pronto."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm sorry but we’re staying here.",
    "answer": "Lo siento pero nos quedamos aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "siento",
      "pero",
      "nos",
      "quedamos",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "siento",
      "pero",
      "nos",
      "quedamos",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We are going to stay near the hotel this afternoon.",
    "answer": "Vamos a quedarnos cerca del hotel esta tarde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "quedarnos",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel",
      "esta",
      "tarde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "quedarnos",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel",
      "esta",
      "tarde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We are staying here because its very late and we’re tired.",
    "answer": "Nos quedamos aquí porque es muy tarde y estamos cansados/as.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Nos",
      "quedamos",
      "aquí",
      "porque",
      "es",
      "muy",
      "tarde",
      "y",
      "estamos",
      "cansados/as."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Nos",
      "quedamos",
      "aquí",
      "porque",
      "es",
      "muy",
      "tarde",
      "y",
      "estamos",
      "cansados/as."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "yourselves (reflexive form)",
    "answer": "os",
    "answerarray": [
      "os"
    ],
    "options": [
      "os"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You get up at 7 o’clock.",
    "answer": "Os levantáis a las siete.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Os",
      "levantáis",
      "a",
      "las",
      "siete."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Os",
      "levantáis",
      "a",
      "las",
      "siete."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you staying here today?",
    "answer": "¿Os quedáis aqui hoy?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Os",
      "quedáis",
      "aqui",
      "hoy?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Os",
      "quedáis",
      "aqui",
      "hoy?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When are you getting up?",
    "answer": "¿Cuándo os levantáis?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "os",
      "levantáis?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "os",
      "levantáis?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do you get up at 6 o’clock?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué os levantáis a la seis?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "os",
      "levantáis",
      "a",
      "la",
      "seis?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "os",
      "levantáis",
      "a",
      "la",
      "seis?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "themselves (reflexive form)",
    "answer": "se",
    "answerarray": [
      "se"
    ],
    "options": [
      "se"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When do they get up?",
    "answer": "¿Cuándo se levantan?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "se",
      "levantan?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "se",
      "levantan?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why don't they stay here?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué no se quedan aquí?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "se",
      "quedan",
      "aquí?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "se",
      "quedan",
      "aquí?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are they getting up soon?",
    "answer": "¿Se levantan pronto?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Se",
      "levantan",
      "pronto?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Se",
      "levantan",
      "pronto?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are staying near the beach this afternoon.",
    "answer": "Se quedan cerca de la playa esta tarde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Se",
      "quedan",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa",
      "esta",
      "tarde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Se",
      "quedan",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa",
      "esta",
      "tarde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to go",
    "answer": "ir",
    "answerarray": [
      "ir"
    ],
    "options": [
      "ir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to do it.",
    "answer": "Voy a hacerlo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "hacerlo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "hacerlo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you going to do it?",
    "answer": "¿Vas a hacerlo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Vas",
      "a",
      "hacerlo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Vas",
      "a",
      "hacerlo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She's going to need it.",
    "answer": "Va a necesitarlo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Va",
      "a",
      "necesitarlo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Va",
      "a",
      "necesitarlo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We're going to Madrid.",
    "answer": "Vamos a Madrid.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "Madrid."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "Madrid."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We’re going to go to Madrid.",
    "answer": "Vamos a ir a Madrid.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "ir",
      "a",
      "Madrid."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "ir",
      "a",
      "Madrid."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) go/are going",
    "answer": "vais",
    "answerarray": [
      "vais"
    ],
    "options": [
      "vais"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "they go/are going",
    "answer": "van",
    "answerarray": [
      "van"
    ],
    "options": [
      "van"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You (plural) are going to do it for me.",
    "answer": "Vais a hacerlo para mí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vais",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vais",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are going to arrive tomorrow.",
    "answer": "Van a llegar mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Van",
      "a",
      "llegar",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Van",
      "a",
      "llegar",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are going to do it too quickly/fast.",
    "answer": "Van a hacerlo demasiado rápido.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Van",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "demasiado",
      "rápido."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Van",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "demasiado",
      "rápido."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of car are they going to need?",
    "answer": "¿Qué tipo de coche van a necesitar?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "tipo",
      "de",
      "coche",
      "van",
      "a",
      "necesitar?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "tipo",
      "de",
      "coche",
      "van",
      "a",
      "necesitar?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to go away/to leave",
    "answer": "irse",
    "answerarray": [
      "irse"
    ],
    "options": [
      "irse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m leaving",
    "answer": "me voy",
    "answerarray": [
      "me",
      "voy"
    ],
    "options": [
      "me",
      "voy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m leaving/going away soon.",
    "answer": "Me voy pronto.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "voy",
      "pronto."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "voy",
      "pronto."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "He’s leaving at eight.",
    "answer": "Se va a las ocho.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Se",
      "va",
      "a",
      "las",
      "ocho."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Se",
      "va",
      "a",
      "las",
      "ocho."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you (singular, informal) leaving now?",
    "answer": "¿Te vas ahora?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Te",
      "vas",
      "ahora?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Te",
      "vas",
      "ahora?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We're leaving tomorrow.",
    "answer": "Nos vamos mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Nos",
      "vamos",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Nos",
      "vamos",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When are you (plural) leaving?",
    "answer": "¿Cuándo os vais?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "os",
      "vais?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuándo",
      "os",
      "vais?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are leaving on Monday.",
    "answer": "Se van el lunes.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Se",
      "van",
      "el",
      "lunes."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Se",
      "van",
      "el",
      "lunes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I would like to leave soon.",
    "answer": "Me gustaría irme pronto.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "gustaría",
      "irme",
      "pronto."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "gustaría",
      "irme",
      "pronto."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You (singular, informal) have to leave now.",
    "answer": "Tienes que irte ahora.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tienes",
      "que",
      "irte",
      "ahora."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tienes",
      "que",
      "irte",
      "ahora."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She doesn't want to leave on Tuesday.",
    "answer": "No quiere irse el martes.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "quiere",
      "irse",
      "el",
      "martes."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "quiere",
      "irse",
      "el",
      "martes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We can’t leave on Wednesday.",
    "answer": "No podemos irnos el miecoles.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "podemos",
      "irnos",
      "el",
      "miecoles."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "podemos",
      "irnos",
      "el",
      "miecoles."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You (plural) have to leave with him.",
    "answer": "Tenéis que iros con el.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tenéis",
      "que",
      "iros",
      "con",
      "el."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tenéis",
      "que",
      "iros",
      "con",
      "el."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How long?",
    "answer": "¿cuánto tiempo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How long are you (singular, informal) staying here?",
    "answer": "¿cuánto tiempo te quedas aqui?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "te",
      "quedas",
      "aqui?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "te",
      "quedas",
      "aqui?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How long are you (plural) staying here?",
    "answer": "¿cuánto tiempo os quedáis aquí?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "os",
      "quedáis",
      "aquí?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "os",
      "quedáis",
      "aquí?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How long are we going to stay here?",
    "answer": "¿cuánto tiempo vamos a quedarnos aquí?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "vamos",
      "a",
      "quedarnos",
      "aquí?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "vamos",
      "a",
      "quedarnos",
      "aquí?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times?",
    "answer": "¿Cuántas veces?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times are you (singular, informal) going to go to the bank today?",
    "answer": "¿Cuántas veces vas a ir al banco hoy?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "vas",
      "a",
      "ir",
      "al",
      "banco",
      "hoy?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "vas",
      "a",
      "ir",
      "al",
      "banco",
      "hoy?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times is she going to call her?",
    "answer": "¿Cuántas veces va a llamarla?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "va",
      "a",
      "llamarla?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Cuántas",
      "veces",
      "va",
      "a",
      "llamarla?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "For how how long do you (singular, informal) need it ?",
    "answer": "¿Para cuánto tiempo lo necesitas?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Para",
      "cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "lo",
      "necesitas?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Para",
      "cuánto",
      "tiempo",
      "lo",
      "necesitas?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm writing it (right now)",
    "answer": "Lo estoy escribiendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "escribiendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "escribiendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are writing it. (right now)",
    "answer": "Lo están escribiendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "están",
      "escribiendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "están",
      "escribiendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm writing it for her because she can’t do it.",
    "answer": "Lo estoy escribiendo para ella porque (ella) no puede hacerlo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "escribiendo",
      "para",
      "ella",
      "porque",
      "(ella)",
      "no",
      "puede",
      "hacerlo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "escribiendo",
      "para",
      "ella",
      "porque",
      "(ella)",
      "no",
      "puede",
      "hacerlo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is she writing it in green?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué lo está escribiendo en verde?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "lo",
      "está",
      "escribiendo",
      "en",
      "verde?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "lo",
      "está",
      "escribiendo",
      "en",
      "verde?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm eating it.",
    "answer": "Lo estoy comiendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "comiendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "estoy",
      "comiendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you (tú) leaving now?",
    "answer": "(salir) ¿Estás saliendo ahora?",
    "answerarray": [
      "(salir)",
      "¿Estás",
      "saliendo",
      "ahora?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "(salir)",
      "¿Estás",
      "saliendo",
      "ahora?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to work",
    "answer": "trabajar",
    "answerarray": [
      "trabajar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "trabajar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I have to work on Sunday.",
    "answer": "Tengo que trabajar el domingo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tengo",
      "que",
      "trabajar",
      "el",
      "domingo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tengo",
      "que",
      "trabajar",
      "el",
      "domingo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I can't speak now because I’m working.",
    "answer": "No puedo hablar ahora porque estoy trabajando.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "puedo",
      "hablar",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "estoy",
      "trabajando."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "puedo",
      "hablar",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "estoy",
      "trabajando."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They don't work on Wednesday.",
    "answer": "No trabajan el miércoles.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "trabajan",
      "el",
      "miércoles."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "trabajan",
      "el",
      "miércoles."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why aren't you working",
    "answer": "¿Por qué no estás trabajando?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "estás",
      "trabajando?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "estás",
      "trabajando?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm working",
    "answer": "trabajo",
    "answerarray": [
      "trabajo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "trabajo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm not working because it’s six o’clock.",
    "answer": "No trabajo porque son las seis.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "trabajo",
      "porque",
      "son",
      "las",
      "seis."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "trabajo",
      "porque",
      "son",
      "las",
      "seis."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm having lunch",
    "answer": "estoy comiendo",
    "answerarray": [
      "estoy",
      "comiendo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "estoy",
      "comiendo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She can’t do it now because she’s having lunch.",
    "answer": "No puede hacerlo ahora porque come. /… está comiendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "puede",
      "hacerlo",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "come.",
      "/…",
      "está",
      "comiendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "puede",
      "hacerlo",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "come.",
      "/…",
      "está",
      "comiendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you doing tonight?",
    "answer": "¿Qué haces esta noche?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "haces",
      "esta",
      "noche?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "haces",
      "esta",
      "noche?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you doing? (right now)",
    "answer": "Qué estás haciendo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Qué",
      "estás",
      "haciendo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Qué",
      "estás",
      "haciendo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is she writing?",
    "answer": "¿Qué está escribiendo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "está",
      "escribiendo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "está",
      "escribiendo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to say/tell",
    "answer": "decir",
    "answerarray": [
      "decir"
    ],
    "options": [
      "decir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you saying?",
    "answer": "¿Qué estás diciendo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estás",
      "diciendo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estás",
      "diciendo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't understand what you are telling me.",
    "answer": "No entiendo lo que me estás diciendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "me",
      "estás",
      "diciendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "me",
      "estás",
      "diciendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't understand why you are not doing it.",
    "answer": "No entiendo porque no lo estás haciendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "estás",
      "haciendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "estás",
      "haciendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a cash machine",
    "answer": "un cajero automático",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "cajero",
      "automático"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "cajero",
      "automático"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to go to the cash machine.",
    "answer": "Necesito ir al cajero automático.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Necesito",
      "ir",
      "al",
      "cajero",
      "automático."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Necesito",
      "ir",
      "al",
      "cajero",
      "automático."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a cash machine near here?",
    "answer": "¿Hay un cajero automático cerca de aquí?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "un",
      "cajero",
      "automático",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "aquí?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "un",
      "cajero",
      "automático",
      "cerca",
      "de",
      "aquí?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are two cash machines in the hotel.",
    "answer": "Hay dos cajeros automáticos en el hotel.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "dos",
      "cajeros",
      "automáticos",
      "en",
      "el",
      "hotel."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "dos",
      "cajeros",
      "automáticos",
      "en",
      "el",
      "hotel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does “cajero automático” mean?",
    "answer": "¿Que quiere decir “cajero automático?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“cajero",
      "automático?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Que",
      "quiere",
      "decir",
      "“cajero",
      "automático?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I have",
    "answer": "tengo",
    "answerarray": [
      "tengo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "tengo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a lot of money.",
    "answer": "Tengo mucho dinero.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tengo",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tengo",
      "mucho",
      "dinero."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don’t have a lot of time.",
    "answer": "No tengo mucho tiempo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "tengo",
      "mucho",
      "tiempo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "tengo",
      "mucho",
      "tiempo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I put/I am putting",
    "answer": "pongo",
    "answerarray": [
      "pongo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "pongo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm putting it on the table.",
    "answer": "Lo pongo en la mesa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "pongo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "pongo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I leave/I am leaving (also: I go out)",
    "answer": "salgo",
    "answerarray": [
      "salgo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "salgo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm leaving now because I have to work.",
    "answer": "Salgo ahora porque tengo que trabajar.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Salgo",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "tengo",
      "que",
      "trabajar."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Salgo",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "tengo",
      "que",
      "trabajar."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I come/I am coming",
    "answer": "vengo",
    "answerarray": [
      "vengo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "vengo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm coming with her tomorrow.",
    "answer": "Vengo con ella mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vengo",
      "con",
      "ella",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vengo",
      "con",
      "ella",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I say/I am saying (also: I tell)",
    "answer": "digo",
    "answerarray": [
      "digo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "digo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm saying it three times because it’s important.",
    "answer": "Lo digo tres veces porque es importante.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "digo",
      "tres",
      "veces",
      "porque",
      "es",
      "importante."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "digo",
      "tres",
      "veces",
      "porque",
      "es",
      "importante."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I do/I am doing",
    "answer": "hago",
    "answerarray": [
      "hago"
    ],
    "options": [
      "hago"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m doing it on Thursday.",
    "answer": "Lo hago el jueves.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "hago",
      "el",
      "jueves."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "hago",
      "el",
      "jueves."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to bring",
    "answer": "traer",
    "answerarray": [
      "traer"
    ],
    "options": [
      "traer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm not bringing it because it’s too big.",
    "answer": "No lo traigo porque es demasiado grande.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "traigo",
      "porque",
      "es",
      "demasiado",
      "grande."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "traigo",
      "porque",
      "es",
      "demasiado",
      "grande."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Go out!",
    "answer": "¡sal!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡sal!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡sal!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don’t go out!",
    "answer": "¡No salgas!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "salgas!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "salgas!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Put it here!",
    "answer": "¡Ponlo aquí!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Ponlo",
      "aquí!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Ponlo",
      "aquí!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't put it there!",
    "answer": "¡No lo pongas allí!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "pongas",
      "allí!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "pongas",
      "allí!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Put on the table!",
    "answer": "¡Ponlo en la mesa!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Ponlo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Ponlo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't put it on the chair!",
    "answer": "¡No lo pongas en la silla!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "pongas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "silla!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "pongas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "silla!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Say it!",
    "answer": "¡Dilo!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Dilo!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Dilo!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't say it!",
    "answer": "¡No lo digas!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "digas!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "digas!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Come with me!",
    "answer": "¡Ven conmigo!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Ven",
      "conmigo!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Ven",
      "conmigo!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't come on Friday!",
    "answer": "¡No vengas el viernes!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "vengas",
      "el",
      "viernes!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "vengas",
      "el",
      "viernes!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it now!",
    "answer": "¡Hazlo ahora!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Hazlo",
      "ahora!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Hazlo",
      "ahora!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't do it with her!",
    "answer": "¡No lo hagas con ella!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "con",
      "ella!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "con",
      "ella!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to bring",
    "answer": "traer",
    "answerarray": [
      "traer"
    ],
    "options": [
      "traer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bring it!",
    "answer": "¡Tráelo!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Tráelo!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Tráelo!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't bring it!",
    "answer": "¡No lo traigas!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "traigas!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "traigas!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don’t put the money on the table.",
    "answer": "No pongas el dinero en la mesa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "el",
      "dinero",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "el",
      "dinero",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don’t put your phone on the chair.",
    "answer": "No pongas tu teléfono en la silla.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "tu",
      "teléfono",
      "en",
      "la",
      "silla."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "tu",
      "teléfono",
      "en",
      "la",
      "silla."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Put the beers on the small table.",
    "answer": "Pon las cervezas en la mesa pequeña.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Pon",
      "las",
      "cervezas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "pequeña."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Pon",
      "las",
      "cervezas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa",
      "pequeña."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't do it now because we’re leaving soon.",
    "answer": "No lo hagas ahora porque nos vamos pronto.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "nos",
      "vamos",
      "pronto."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "nos",
      "vamos",
      "pronto."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it later because we’re not staying here.",
    "answer": "Hazlo más tarde porque no nos quedamos aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hazlo",
      "más",
      "tarde",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "nos",
      "quedamos",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hazlo",
      "más",
      "tarde",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "nos",
      "quedamos",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Say it slowly.",
    "answer": "Dilo despacio.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Dilo",
      "despacio."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Dilo",
      "despacio."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Say it more slowly because she doesn’t understand English.",
    "answer": "Dilo más despacio porque no entiende inglés.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Dilo",
      "más",
      "despacio",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "entiende",
      "inglés."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Dilo",
      "más",
      "despacio",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "entiende",
      "inglés."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't say that!",
    "answer": "¡No digas eso!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "digas",
      "eso!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "digas",
      "eso!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Say this!",
    "answer": "¡Di esto!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Di",
      "esto!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Di",
      "esto!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't come if you don’t want (to).",
    "answer": "No vengas si no quieres.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "vengas",
      "si",
      "no",
      "quieres."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "vengas",
      "si",
      "no",
      "quieres."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't come if it’s too difficult for you.",
    "answer": "No vengas si es demasiado difícil para ti.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "vengas",
      "si",
      "es",
      "demasiado",
      "difícil",
      "para",
      "ti."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "vengas",
      "si",
      "es",
      "demasiado",
      "difícil",
      "para",
      "ti."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't do it if you don’t like it.",
    "answer": "No lo hagas si no te gusta.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "si",
      "no",
      "te",
      "gusta."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "si",
      "no",
      "te",
      "gusta."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Come now because we’re starting.",
    "answer": "Ven ahora porque estamos empezando.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Ven",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "estamos",
      "empezando."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Ven",
      "ahora",
      "porque",
      "estamos",
      "empezando."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't come now. It’s too late.",
    "answer": "No vengas ahora. Es demasiado tarde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "vengas",
      "ahora.",
      "Es",
      "demasiado",
      "tarde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "vengas",
      "ahora.",
      "Es",
      "demasiado",
      "tarde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't do it today. It’s not important.",
    "answer": "No lo hagas hoy. No es importante.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "hoy.",
      "No",
      "es",
      "importante."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "hoy.",
      "No",
      "es",
      "importante."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't do it like that!",
    "answer": "¡No lo hagas así!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "así!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "así!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Come here! I want to tell you something.",
    "answer": "¡Ven aquí! Quiero decirte algo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Ven",
      "aquí!",
      "Quiero",
      "decirte",
      "algo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Ven",
      "aquí!",
      "Quiero",
      "decirte",
      "algo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do number two first. It’s easier.",
    "answer": "Haz el número dos primero. Es más fácil",
    "answerarray": [
      "Haz",
      "el",
      "número",
      "dos",
      "primero.",
      "Es",
      "más",
      "fácil"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Haz",
      "el",
      "número",
      "dos",
      "primero.",
      "Es",
      "más",
      "fácil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Leave now!",
    "answer": "¡Sal ahora!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Sal",
      "ahora!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Sal",
      "ahora!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't leave now if you want to see her.",
    "answer": "No salgas ahora si quieres verla.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "salgas",
      "ahora",
      "si",
      "quieres",
      "verla."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "salgas",
      "ahora",
      "si",
      "quieres",
      "verla."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "next to",
    "answer": "al lado de",
    "answerarray": [
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de"
    ],
    "options": [
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I live next to the market.",
    "answer": "Vivo al lado del mercado.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vivo",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "del",
      "mercado."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vivo",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "del",
      "mercado."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "My car is next to the house.",
    "answer": "Mi coche está al lado de la casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Mi",
      "coche",
      "está",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Mi",
      "coche",
      "está",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There's a a small restaurant next to the hotel.",
    "answer": "Hay un restaurante pequeño al lado del hotel.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "restaurante",
      "pequeño",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "restaurante",
      "pequeño",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "He works in a supermarket.",
    "answer": "Trabaja en un supermercado.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Trabaja",
      "en",
      "un",
      "supermercado."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Trabaja",
      "en",
      "un",
      "supermercado."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where’s the supermarket?",
    "answer": "¿Dónde está el supermercado?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Dónde",
      "está",
      "el",
      "supermercado?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Dónde",
      "está",
      "el",
      "supermercado?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's next to the beach.",
    "answer": "Está al lado de la playa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Está",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Está",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "la",
      "playa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to wait (for)",
    "answer": "esperar",
    "answerarray": [
      "esperar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "esperar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I am waiting for something.",
    "answer": "Estoy esperando algo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "esperando",
      "algo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "esperando",
      "algo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wait for me.",
    "answer": "Espérame.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Espérame."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Espérame."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wait for me next to the swimming pool.",
    "answer": "Espérame al lado de la piscina.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Espérame",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "la",
      "piscina."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Espérame",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "la",
      "piscina."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm waiting for the car.",
    "answer": "Estoy esperando el coche.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "esperando",
      "el",
      "coche."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "esperando",
      "el",
      "coche."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wait for her.",
    "answer": "Espérala.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Espérala."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Espérala."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wait for him in front of the hotel.",
    "answer": "Espéralo delante del hotel.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Espéralo",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Espéralo",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a day",
    "answer": "un día",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "día"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "día"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(for) two days",
    "answer": "dos dias",
    "answerarray": [
      "dos",
      "dias"
    ],
    "options": [
      "dos",
      "dias"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wait two days.",
    "answer": "Espera dos dias.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Espera",
      "dos",
      "dias."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Espera",
      "dos",
      "dias."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to wait for three days.",
    "answer": "Voy a esperar tres dias.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "esperar",
      "tres",
      "dias."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "esperar",
      "tres",
      "dias."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a week",
    "answer": "una semana",
    "answerarray": [
      "una",
      "semana"
    ],
    "options": [
      "una",
      "semana"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We’re here (for) a week.",
    "answer": "Estamos aquí una semana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estamos",
      "aquí",
      "una",
      "semana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estamos",
      "aquí",
      "una",
      "semana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We're going to Spain for three weeks.",
    "answer": "Vamos a España tres semanas.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "España",
      "tres",
      "semanas."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "España",
      "tres",
      "semanas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to wait a week and if it doesn’t arrive, I’m going to call.",
    "answer": "Voy a esperar una semana y si no llega, voy a llamar.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "esperar",
      "una",
      "semana",
      "y",
      "si",
      "no",
      "llega,",
      "voy",
      "a",
      "llamar."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "esperar",
      "una",
      "semana",
      "y",
      "si",
      "no",
      "llega,",
      "voy",
      "a",
      "llamar."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "an hour",
    "answer": "una hora",
    "answerarray": [
      "una",
      "hora"
    ],
    "options": [
      "una",
      "hora"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m leaving in a an hour.",
    "answer": "Me Salgo en una hora.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "Salgo",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "Salgo",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Come in an hour.",
    "answer": "Ven en una hora.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Ven",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Ven",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I can do it in two hours.",
    "answer": "Puedo hacerlo en dos horas.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Puedo",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "dos",
      "horas."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Puedo",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "dos",
      "horas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I can do it in two hours.",
    "answer": "Puedo hacerlo en dos horas.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Puedo",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "dos",
      "horas."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Puedo",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "dos",
      "horas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I would like to sell it in two weeks.",
    "answer": "Me gustaría venderlo en dos semanas.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "gustaría",
      "venderlo",
      "en",
      "dos",
      "semanas."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "gustaría",
      "venderlo",
      "en",
      "dos",
      "semanas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Call her in an hour.",
    "answer": "Llámala en una hora.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Llámala",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Llámala",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you do it quickly you can do it in a week.",
    "answer": "Si lo haces rápido, puedes hacerlo en una semana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Si",
      "lo",
      "haces",
      "rápido,",
      "puedes",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "una",
      "semana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Si",
      "lo",
      "haces",
      "rápido,",
      "puedes",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "una",
      "semana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to come back/return",
    "answer": "volver",
    "answerarray": [
      "volver"
    ],
    "options": [
      "volver"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We are coming back in four days (time).",
    "answer": "Volvemos en quatro días.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Volvemos",
      "en",
      "quatro",
      "días."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Volvemos",
      "en",
      "quatro",
      "días."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you don’t come back in an hour, I’m not going to wait for you.",
    "answer": "Si no vuelves en una hora, no voy a esperarte.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Si",
      "no",
      "vuelves",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora,",
      "no",
      "voy",
      "a",
      "esperarte."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Si",
      "no",
      "vuelves",
      "en",
      "una",
      "hora,",
      "no",
      "voy",
      "a",
      "esperarte."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We can't do it this week.",
    "answer": "No podemos hacerlo esta semana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "podemos",
      "hacerlo",
      "esta",
      "semana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "podemos",
      "hacerlo",
      "esta",
      "semana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "next week",
    "answer": "la semana que viene",
    "answerarray": [
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene"
    ],
    "options": [
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We are going to do it next week.",
    "answer": "Vamos a hacerlo la semana que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I wouldn’t like to be here next week.",
    "answer": "No me gustaría estar aquí la semana que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "gustaría",
      "estar",
      "aquí",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "gustaría",
      "estar",
      "aquí",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to sell it next week.",
    "answer": "Voy a venderlo la semana que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "venderlo",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "venderlo",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why don't you sell it this week?",
    "answer": "¿Por qué no lo vendes esta semana?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "vendes",
      "esta",
      "semana?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Por",
      "qué",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "vendes",
      "esta",
      "semana?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a year",
    "answer": "un año",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "año"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "año"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "next year",
    "answer": "el año que viene",
    "answerarray": [
      "el",
      "año",
      "que",
      "viene"
    ],
    "options": [
      "el",
      "año",
      "que",
      "viene"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it next year.",
    "answer": "Hazlo el año que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hazlo",
      "el",
      "año",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hazlo",
      "el",
      "año",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't do it this year.",
    "answer": "No lo hagas este año.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "este",
      "año."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "este",
      "año."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to buy a new house next year.",
    "answer": "Quiero comprar una casa nueva el año que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Quiero",
      "comprar",
      "una",
      "casa",
      "nueva",
      "el",
      "año",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Quiero",
      "comprar",
      "una",
      "casa",
      "nueva",
      "el",
      "año",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I talk (speak) to you next week?",
    "answer": "¿Puedo hablar contigo la semana que viene?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Puedo",
      "hablar",
      "contigo",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Puedo",
      "hablar",
      "contigo",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We can't start this week because it’s not ready.",
    "answer": "No podemos empezar esta semana porque no está listo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "podemos",
      "empezar",
      "esta",
      "semana",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "está",
      "listo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "podemos",
      "empezar",
      "esta",
      "semana",
      "porque",
      "no",
      "está",
      "listo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to give",
    "answer": "dar",
    "answerarray": [
      "dar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "dar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You can give me the money next week.",
    "answer": "Puedes darme el dinero la semana que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Puedes",
      "darme",
      "el",
      "dinero",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Puedes",
      "darme",
      "el",
      "dinero",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "He's giving me the book next week.",
    "answer": "Me da el libro la semana que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "da",
      "el",
      "libro",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "da",
      "el",
      "libro",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's very late.",
    "answer": "Es muy tarde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Es",
      "muy",
      "tarde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Es",
      "muy",
      "tarde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes. See you tomorrow. Good night.",
    "answer": "Si. Hasta mañana. Buenas noches.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Si.",
      "Hasta",
      "mañana.",
      "Buenas",
      "noches."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Si.",
      "Hasta",
      "mañana.",
      "Buenas",
      "noches."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "more",
    "answer": "más",
    "answerarray": [
      "más"
    ],
    "options": [
      "más"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "more than",
    "answer": "más que",
    "answerarray": [
      "más",
      "que"
    ],
    "options": [
      "más",
      "que"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I eat more than you.",
    "answer": "Como mas que tú.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Como",
      "mas",
      "que",
      "tú."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Como",
      "mas",
      "que",
      "tú."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have more money than me (I).",
    "answer": "Tienes más dinero que yo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tienes",
      "más",
      "dinero",
      "que",
      "yo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tienes",
      "más",
      "dinero",
      "que",
      "yo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "She gives me more than than you.",
    "answer": "Me da más que tú.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "da",
      "más",
      "que",
      "tú."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "da",
      "más",
      "que",
      "tú."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I write more than Carlos.",
    "answer": "Escribo más que Carlos.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Escribo",
      "más",
      "que",
      "Carlos."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Escribo",
      "más",
      "que",
      "Carlos."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "He works more than me.",
    "answer": "Trabaja más que yo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Trabaja",
      "más",
      "que",
      "yo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Trabaja",
      "más",
      "que",
      "yo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I like the red book more than the green one.",
    "answer": "Me gusta el libro rojo más que el verde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Me",
      "gusta",
      "el",
      "libro",
      "rojo",
      "más",
      "que",
      "el",
      "verde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Me",
      "gusta",
      "el",
      "libro",
      "rojo",
      "más",
      "que",
      "el",
      "verde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The white computer is more expensive than the black one.",
    "answer": "El ordenador blanco es más caro que el negro.",
    "answerarray": [
      "El",
      "ordenador",
      "blanco",
      "es",
      "más",
      "caro",
      "que",
      "el",
      "negro."
    ],
    "options": [
      "El",
      "ordenador",
      "blanco",
      "es",
      "más",
      "caro",
      "que",
      "el",
      "negro."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The restaurant is nearer the hotel than the swimming pool.",
    "answer": "EL restaurante esta más cerca del hotel que la piscina.",
    "answerarray": [
      "EL",
      "restaurante",
      "esta",
      "más",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel",
      "que",
      "la",
      "piscina."
    ],
    "options": [
      "EL",
      "restaurante",
      "esta",
      "más",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel",
      "que",
      "la",
      "piscina."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "less than",
    "answer": "menos que",
    "answerarray": [
      "menos",
      "que"
    ],
    "options": [
      "menos",
      "que"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I eat less than you.",
    "answer": "Como menos que tú.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Como",
      "menos",
      "que",
      "tú."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Como",
      "menos",
      "que",
      "tú."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I have less time today that on Saturday.",
    "answer": "Tengo menos tiempo hoy que el sábado.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tengo",
      "menos",
      "tiempo",
      "hoy",
      "que",
      "el",
      "sábado."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tengo",
      "menos",
      "tiempo",
      "hoy",
      "que",
      "el",
      "sábado."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is less beer than Coca Cola.",
    "answer": "Hay menos cerveza que Coca Cola.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "menos",
      "cerveza",
      "que",
      "Coca",
      "Cola."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "menos",
      "cerveza",
      "que",
      "Coca",
      "Cola."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are less men than women here.",
    "answer": "Hay menos hombres que mujeres aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "menos",
      "hombres",
      "que",
      "mujeres",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "menos",
      "hombres",
      "que",
      "mujeres",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I speak more Spanish than him, but less than her.",
    "answer": "Hablo mas español que él, pero menos que ella.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hablo",
      "mas",
      "español",
      "que",
      "él,",
      "pero",
      "menos",
      "que",
      "ella."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hablo",
      "mas",
      "español",
      "que",
      "él,",
      "pero",
      "menos",
      "que",
      "ella."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't tell me now tell me later (more late).",
    "answer": "No me digas ahora, dime más tarde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "digas",
      "ahora,",
      "dime",
      "más",
      "tarde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "digas",
      "ahora,",
      "dime",
      "más",
      "tarde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to speak",
    "answer": "hablar",
    "answerarray": [
      "hablar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "hablar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Speak!",
    "answer": "¡Habla!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Habla!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Habla!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't speak!",
    "answer": "¡No hables!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "hables!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "hables!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to work",
    "answer": "trabajar",
    "answerarray": [
      "trabajar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "trabajar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Work!",
    "answer": "¡Trabaja!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Trabaja!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Trabaja!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't work!",
    "answer": "¡No trabajes!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "trabajes!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "trabajes!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to start",
    "answer": "empezar",
    "answerarray": [
      "empezar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "empezar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Start now!",
    "answer": "¡Empieza ahora!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Empieza",
      "ahora!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Empieza",
      "ahora!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't start!",
    "answer": "¡No empieces!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "empieces!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "empieces!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Call me!",
    "answer": "¡Llámame!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Llámame!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Llámame!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't call me because I’m busy.",
    "answer": "No me llames porque estoy ocupado/a.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "llames",
      "porque",
      "estoy",
      "ocupado/a."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "me",
      "llames",
      "porque",
      "estoy",
      "ocupado/a."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't start if you are not ready",
    "answer": "No empieces si no estas listo/a.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "empieces",
      "si",
      "no",
      "estas",
      "listo/a."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "empieces",
      "si",
      "no",
      "estas",
      "listo/a."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't work if you are tired.",
    "answer": "No trabajes si estas cansado/a.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "trabajes",
      "si",
      "estas",
      "cansado/a."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "trabajes",
      "si",
      "estas",
      "cansado/a."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to come back",
    "answer": "volver",
    "answerarray": [
      "volver"
    ],
    "options": [
      "volver"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Come back tomorrow!",
    "answer": "¡Vuelve mañana!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Vuelve",
      "mañana!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Vuelve",
      "mañana!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't come back tonight!",
    "answer": "¡No vuelvas esta noche!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "vuelvas",
      "esta",
      "noche!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "vuelvas",
      "esta",
      "noche!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to eat",
    "answer": "comer",
    "answerarray": [
      "comer"
    ],
    "options": [
      "comer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eat it!",
    "answer": "¡Cómelo!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Cómelo!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Cómelo!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't eat it!",
    "answer": "¡No lo comas!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "comas!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "comas!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to sell",
    "answer": "vender",
    "answerarray": [
      "vender"
    ],
    "options": [
      "vender"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sell it!",
    "answer": "¡Véndelo!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Véndelo!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Véndelo!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't sell it!",
    "answer": "¡No lo vendas!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "vendas!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡No",
      "lo",
      "vendas!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to write",
    "answer": "escribir",
    "answerarray": [
      "escribir"
    ],
    "options": [
      "escribir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Write your name here.",
    "answer": "Escribe tu nombre aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Escribe",
      "tu",
      "nombre",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Escribe",
      "tu",
      "nombre",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don’t write it in red.",
    "answer": "No lo escribas en rojo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "escribas",
      "en",
      "rojo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "lo",
      "escribas",
      "en",
      "rojo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't eat the green one.",
    "answer": "No comas el verde.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "comas",
      "el",
      "verde."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "comas",
      "el",
      "verde."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eat the yellow one.",
    "answer": "Come el amarillo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Come",
      "el",
      "amarillo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Come",
      "el",
      "amarillo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't put the red one on the table.",
    "answer": "No pongas el rojo en la mesa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "el",
      "rojo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "el",
      "rojo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the (plural)",
    "answer": "los/las",
    "answerarray": [
      "los/las"
    ],
    "options": [
      "los/las"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the chairs",
    "answer": "las sillas",
    "answerarray": [
      "las",
      "sillas"
    ],
    "options": [
      "las",
      "sillas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the cars",
    "answer": "los carros",
    "answerarray": [
      "los",
      "carros"
    ],
    "options": [
      "los",
      "carros"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Put the chairs on the table.",
    "answer": "Pon las sillas en la mesa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Pon",
      "las",
      "sillas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Pon",
      "las",
      "sillas",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't speak to the men.",
    "answer": "No hables con los hombres.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hables",
      "con",
      "los",
      "hombres."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hables",
      "con",
      "los",
      "hombres."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The women are coming next week.",
    "answer": "Las mujeres vienen la semana que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Las",
      "mujeres",
      "vienen",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Las",
      "mujeres",
      "vienen",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The women eat less than the men.",
    "answer": "Las mujeres comen menos que los hombres.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Las",
      "mujeres",
      "comen",
      "menos",
      "que",
      "los",
      "hombres."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Las",
      "mujeres",
      "comen",
      "menos",
      "que",
      "los",
      "hombres."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the red cars",
    "answer": "los coches rojos",
    "answerarray": [
      "los",
      "coches",
      "rojos"
    ],
    "options": [
      "los",
      "coches",
      "rojos"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the red chairs",
    "answer": "las sillas rojas",
    "answerarray": [
      "las",
      "sillas",
      "rojas"
    ],
    "options": [
      "las",
      "sillas",
      "rojas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the important women",
    "answer": "las mujeres importantes",
    "answerarray": [
      "las",
      "mujeres",
      "importantes"
    ],
    "options": [
      "las",
      "mujeres",
      "importantes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "the big tables",
    "answer": "las mesas grandes",
    "answerarray": [
      "las",
      "mesas",
      "grandes"
    ],
    "options": [
      "las",
      "mesas",
      "grandes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The yellow chairs are next to the small tables.",
    "answer": "Las sillas amarillas están al lado de las mesas pequeñas.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Las",
      "sillas",
      "amarillas",
      "están",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "las",
      "mesas",
      "pequeñas."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Las",
      "sillas",
      "amarillas",
      "están",
      "al",
      "lado",
      "de",
      "las",
      "mesas",
      "pequeñas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it once, but don’t do it twice.",
    "answer": "Hazlo una vez, pero no lo hagas dos veces.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hazlo",
      "una",
      "vez,",
      "pero",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "dos",
      "veces."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hazlo",
      "una",
      "vez,",
      "pero",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "hagas",
      "dos",
      "veces."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Say it twice, but don’t say it three times.",
    "answer": "Dilo dos veces, pero no lo digas tres veces.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Dilo",
      "dos",
      "veces,",
      "pero",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "digas",
      "tres",
      "veces."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Dilo",
      "dos",
      "veces,",
      "pero",
      "no",
      "lo",
      "digas",
      "tres",
      "veces."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a thing",
    "answer": "una cosa",
    "answerarray": [
      "una",
      "cosa"
    ],
    "options": [
      "una",
      "cosa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's that thing?",
    "answer": "¿Qué es esa cosa?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "es",
      "esa",
      "cosa?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "es",
      "esa",
      "cosa?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are three things that I want to tell you.",
    "answer": "Hay tres cosas que quiero decirte.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "tres",
      "cosas",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "decirte."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "tres",
      "cosas",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "decirte."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I only do the important things.",
    "answer": "Solo hago las cosas importantes.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Solo",
      "hago",
      "las",
      "cosas",
      "importantes."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Solo",
      "hago",
      "las",
      "cosas",
      "importantes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "some, a few",
    "answer": "unos, unas",
    "answerarray": [
      "unos,",
      "unas"
    ],
    "options": [
      "unos,",
      "unas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a few things",
    "answer": "unas cosas",
    "answerarray": [
      "unas",
      "cosas"
    ],
    "options": [
      "unas",
      "cosas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a few things in the car.",
    "answer": "Tengo unas cosas en el coche.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Tengo",
      "unas",
      "cosas",
      "en",
      "el",
      "coche."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Tengo",
      "unas",
      "cosas",
      "en",
      "el",
      "coche."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m putting a few things behind the table.",
    "answer": "Estoy poniendo/pongo unas cosas detrás de la mesa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "poniendo/pongo",
      "unas",
      "cosas",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "poniendo/pongo",
      "unas",
      "cosas",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a few days",
    "answer": "unos días",
    "answerarray": [
      "unos",
      "días"
    ],
    "options": [
      "unos",
      "días"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to do it in a few days.",
    "answer": "Voy a hacerlo en unos días.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "unos",
      "días."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "hacerlo",
      "en",
      "unos",
      "días."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We are going to be here a few weeks.",
    "answer": "Vamos a estar aquí unas semanas.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "estar",
      "aquí",
      "unas",
      "semanas."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Vamos",
      "a",
      "estar",
      "aquí",
      "unas",
      "semanas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are going to stay in Barcelona (for) a few hours",
    "answer": "Van a quedarse en Barcelona unas horas.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Van",
      "a",
      "quedarse",
      "en",
      "Barcelona",
      "unas",
      "horas."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Van",
      "a",
      "quedarse",
      "en",
      "Barcelona",
      "unas",
      "horas."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The women are staying here a few days more.",
    "answer": "Las mujeres se quedan aquí unos días más.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Las",
      "mujeres",
      "se",
      "quedan",
      "aquí",
      "unos",
      "días",
      "más."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Las",
      "mujeres",
      "se",
      "quedan",
      "aquí",
      "unos",
      "días",
      "más."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "you (polite)",
    "answer": "usted",
    "answerarray": [
      "usted"
    ],
    "options": [
      "usted"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you tell me where the beech is?",
    "answer": "¿Puede (usted) decirme dónde está la playa?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Puede",
      "(usted)",
      "decirme",
      "dónde",
      "está",
      "la",
      "playa?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Puede",
      "(usted)",
      "decirme",
      "dónde",
      "está",
      "la",
      "playa?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sir/madam",
    "answer": "señor/señora",
    "answerarray": [
      "señor/señora"
    ],
    "options": [
      "señor/señora"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Excuse me.",
    "answer": "perdón/perdone",
    "answerarray": [
      "perdón/perdone"
    ],
    "options": [
      "perdón/perdone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Excuse me, madam, Do you know where there is a bank?",
    "answer": "Perdón, señora. ¿Sabe dónde hay un banco?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Perdón,",
      "señora.",
      "¿Sabe",
      "dónde",
      "hay",
      "un",
      "banco?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Perdón,",
      "señora.",
      "¿Sabe",
      "dónde",
      "hay",
      "un",
      "banco?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a train",
    "answer": "un tren",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "tren"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "tren"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a bus",
    "answer": "un autobús",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "autobús"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "autobús"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Excuse me, sir. Do you know at what time the bus leaves?",
    "answer": "Perdón, señor. ¿Sabe a qué hora sale el bus?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Perdón,",
      "señor.",
      "¿Sabe",
      "a",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "el",
      "bus?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Perdón,",
      "señor.",
      "¿Sabe",
      "a",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "el",
      "bus?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Excuse me, madam. Can you tell me when the train arrives?",
    "answer": "Perdón, señora. ¿Puede decirme cuando llega el tren?",
    "answerarray": [
      "Perdón,",
      "señora.",
      "¿Puede",
      "decirme",
      "cuando",
      "llega",
      "el",
      "tren?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Perdón,",
      "señora.",
      "¿Puede",
      "decirme",
      "cuando",
      "llega",
      "el",
      "tren?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a train that goes to Valencia today?",
    "answer": "¿Hay un tren que va a Valencia hoy?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "un",
      "tren",
      "que",
      "va",
      "a",
      "Valencia",
      "hoy?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "un",
      "tren",
      "que",
      "va",
      "a",
      "Valencia",
      "hoy?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are fewer buses on Sunday than on Saturday.",
    "answer": "Hay menos buses el domingo que el sábado.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "menos",
      "buses",
      "el",
      "domingo",
      "que",
      "el",
      "sábado."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "menos",
      "buses",
      "el",
      "domingo",
      "que",
      "el",
      "sábado."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "in the morning, afternoon, evening",
    "answer": "por la mañana, tarde, noche",
    "answerarray": [
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana,",
      "tarde,",
      "noche"
    ],
    "options": [
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana,",
      "tarde,",
      "noche"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a bus in the morning.",
    "answer": "Hay un bus por la mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "bus",
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "bus",
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a train in the afternoon?",
    "answer": "¿Hay un tren por la tarde?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "un",
      "tren",
      "por",
      "la",
      "tarde?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "un",
      "tren",
      "por",
      "la",
      "tarde?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There aren't (any) buses at night.",
    "answer": "No hay buses por la noche.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "buses",
      "por",
      "la",
      "noche."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "buses",
      "por",
      "la",
      "noche."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a plane",
    "answer": "un avion",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "avion"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "avion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time does your plane leave?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora sale tu avión?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "tu",
      "avión?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "tu",
      "avión?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time does her plane leave?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora sale su avión?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "su",
      "avión?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "su",
      "avión?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time does his plane leave?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora sale su avión?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "su",
      "avión?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "su",
      "avión?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "your (formal)",
    "answer": "su",
    "answerarray": [
      "su"
    ],
    "options": [
      "su"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time does your (formal) plane leave?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora sale su avión?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "su",
      "avión?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "sale",
      "su",
      "avión?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your (formal) train arrives in the morning.",
    "answer": "Su tren llega por la mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Su",
      "tren",
      "llega",
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "tren",
      "llega",
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is nothing in your (formal) car.",
    "answer": "No hay nada en su coche.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "en",
      "su",
      "coche."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "en",
      "su",
      "coche."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are a few things in your room, madam.",
    "answer": "Hay unas cosas en su habitación, señora.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "unas",
      "cosas",
      "en",
      "su",
      "habitación,",
      "señora."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "unas",
      "cosas",
      "en",
      "su",
      "habitación,",
      "señora."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There’s a plane that goes to Mallorca next week.",
    "answer": "Hay un avión que va a Mallorca la semana que viene.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "avión",
      "que",
      "va",
      "a",
      "Mallorca",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "avión",
      "que",
      "va",
      "a",
      "Mallorca",
      "la",
      "semana",
      "que",
      "viene."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a train that goes to Alicante in the morning.",
    "answer": "Hay un tren que va a Alicante por la mañana.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "tren",
      "que",
      "va",
      "a",
      "Alicante",
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "tren",
      "que",
      "va",
      "a",
      "Alicante",
      "por",
      "la",
      "mañana."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This method is very difficult.",
    "answer": "Este método es muy difícil.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Este",
      "método",
      "es",
      "muy",
      "difícil."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Este",
      "método",
      "es",
      "muy",
      "difícil."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I find it easy but it goes too slowly.",
    "answer": "Lo encuentro fácil pero va demasiado despacio.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "encuentro",
      "fácil",
      "pero",
      "va",
      "demasiado",
      "despacio."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "encuentro",
      "fácil",
      "pero",
      "va",
      "demasiado",
      "despacio."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's too fast for me.",
    "answer": "Es demasiado rápido para mí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Es",
      "demasiado",
      "rápido",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Es",
      "demasiado",
      "rápido",
      "para",
      "mí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you very much.",
    "answer": "Muchas gracias.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Muchas",
      "gracias."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Muchas",
      "gracias."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "See you soon!",
    "answer": "¡Hasta pronto!",
    "answerarray": [
      "¡Hasta",
      "pronto!"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¡Hasta",
      "pronto!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m doing",
    "answer": "estoy haciendo",
    "answerarray": [
      "estoy",
      "haciendo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "estoy",
      "haciendo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m leaving/going out",
    "answer": "estoy saliendo",
    "answerarray": [
      "estoy",
      "saliendo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "estoy",
      "saliendo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I’m speaking",
    "answer": "estoy hablando",
    "answerarray": [
      "estoy",
      "hablando"
    ],
    "options": [
      "estoy",
      "hablando"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm leaving now.",
    "answer": "Estoy saliendo ahora.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "saliendo",
      "ahora."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "saliendo",
      "ahora."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm putting the chair on the table.",
    "answer": "Estoy poniendo la silla en la mesa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "poniendo",
      "la",
      "silla",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "poniendo",
      "la",
      "silla",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Are you having lunch now?",
    "answer": "¿Estás comiendo ahora?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Estás",
      "comiendo",
      "ahora?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Estás",
      "comiendo",
      "ahora?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's starting now.",
    "answer": "Está empezando ahora",
    "answerarray": [
      "Está",
      "empezando",
      "ahora"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Está",
      "empezando",
      "ahora"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you doing?",
    "answer": "¿Qué estás haciendo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estás",
      "haciendo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estás",
      "haciendo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you saying?",
    "answer": "¿Qué estás diciendo?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estás",
      "diciendo?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "estás",
      "diciendo?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "…what…",
    "answer": "…lo que…",
    "answerarray": [
      "…lo",
      "que…"
    ],
    "options": [
      "…lo",
      "que…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm sorry but I don’t understand what you are saying.",
    "answer": "Lo siento pero no entiendo lo que estás diciendo.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Lo",
      "siento",
      "pero",
      "no",
      "entiendo",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "estás",
      "diciendo."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Lo",
      "siento",
      "pero",
      "no",
      "entiendo",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "estás",
      "diciendo."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't know what you want,",
    "answer": "No sé lo que quieres.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "sé",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quieres."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "sé",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quieres."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's not what I want.",
    "answer": "No es lo que quiero.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "es",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiero."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "es",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiero."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I can’t find what I want here.",
    "answer": "No puedo encontrar lo que quiero aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "puedo",
      "encontrar",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "puedo",
      "encontrar",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you want to say?",
    "answer": "¿Qué quieres decir?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quieres",
      "decir?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quieres",
      "decir?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you mean?",
    "answer": "¿Qué quieres decir?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quieres",
      "decir?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Qué",
      "quieres",
      "decir?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't understand very well what you mean.",
    "answer": "No entiendo muy bien lo que quieres decir.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "muy",
      "bien",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quieres",
      "decir."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "entiendo",
      "muy",
      "bien",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quieres",
      "decir."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm sure (that) you don’t know what I mean.",
    "answer": "Estoy seguro que no sabes lo que quiero decir.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "seguro",
      "que",
      "no",
      "sabes",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "decir."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "seguro",
      "que",
      "no",
      "sabes",
      "lo",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "decir."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "to arrive/to get to",
    "answer": "llegar",
    "answerarray": [
      "llegar"
    ],
    "options": [
      "llegar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I am arriving now.",
    "answer": "Estoy llegando ahora.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Estoy",
      "llegando",
      "ahora."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Estoy",
      "llegando",
      "ahora."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "at one o’clock",
    "answer": "a la una",
    "answerarray": [
      "a",
      "la",
      "una"
    ],
    "options": [
      "a",
      "la",
      "una"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time do you arrive?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora llegas?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "llegas?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "llegas?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I arrive at one o’clock.",
    "answer": "Llego a la una.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Llego",
      "a",
      "la",
      "una."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Llego",
      "a",
      "la",
      "una."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "at two o’clock",
    "answer": "a las dos",
    "answerarray": [
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos"
    ],
    "options": [
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time does he arrive?",
    "answer": "¿A qué hora llega?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "llega?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿A",
      "qué",
      "hora",
      "llega?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "He arrives at two o’clock.",
    "answer": "Llega a las dos.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Llega",
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Llega",
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does she arrive at two o’clock or at three o’clock?",
    "answer": "¿Llega a las dos o a las tres?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Llega",
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos",
      "o",
      "a",
      "las",
      "tres?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Llega",
      "a",
      "las",
      "dos",
      "o",
      "a",
      "las",
      "tres?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I think (that) he she arrives at four o’clock.",
    "answer": "Pienso que llega a las cuatro.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Pienso",
      "que",
      "llega",
      "a",
      "las",
      "cuatro."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Pienso",
      "que",
      "llega",
      "a",
      "las",
      "cuatro."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I find that it’s not easy to get (arrive) to your house.",
    "answer": "Encuentro que no es fácil llegar a tu casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Encuentro",
      "que",
      "no",
      "es",
      "fácil",
      "llegar",
      "a",
      "tu",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Encuentro",
      "que",
      "no",
      "es",
      "fácil",
      "llegar",
      "a",
      "tu",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "something",
    "answer": "algo",
    "answerarray": [
      "algo"
    ],
    "options": [
      "algo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing",
    "answer": "nada",
    "answerarray": [
      "nada"
    ],
    "options": [
      "nada"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is something blue on the table.",
    "answer": "Hay algo azul en la mesa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "algo",
      "azul",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "algo",
      "azul",
      "en",
      "la",
      "mesa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nothing is going to be ready today.",
    "answer": "Nada va a estar listo hoy.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Nada",
      "va",
      "a",
      "estar",
      "listo",
      "hoy."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Nada",
      "va",
      "a",
      "estar",
      "listo",
      "hoy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is nothing in the room.",
    "answer": "No hay nada en la habitación.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "en",
      "la",
      "habitación."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "en",
      "la",
      "habitación."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is nothing in the house.",
    "answer": "No hay nada en la casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "en",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "en",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is nothing that I want to do here.",
    "answer": "No hay nada que quiero hacer aquí.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "hacer",
      "aquí."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "que",
      "quiero",
      "hacer",
      "aquí."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't want to do anything.",
    "answer": "No quiero hacer nada.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "quiero",
      "hacer",
      "nada."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "quiero",
      "hacer",
      "nada."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to say something important.",
    "answer": "Voy a decir algo importante.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "decir",
      "algo",
      "importante."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Voy",
      "a",
      "decir",
      "algo",
      "importante."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "in front of",
    "answer": "delante de",
    "answerarray": [
      "delante",
      "de"
    ],
    "options": [
      "delante",
      "de"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "behind",
    "answer": "detrás de",
    "answerarray": [
      "detrás",
      "de"
    ],
    "options": [
      "detrás",
      "de"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is something behind the house.",
    "answer": "Hay algo detrás de la casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "algo",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "algo",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "la",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is something in front of car.",
    "answer": "Hay algo delante del coche.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "algo",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "coche."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "algo",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "coche."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is nothing behind the woman.",
    "answer": "No hay nada detrás de la mujer.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "la",
      "mujer."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "la",
      "mujer."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There's nothing in front of the man.",
    "answer": "No hay nada delante del hombre.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "hombre."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "nada",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "hombre."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something in the room?",
    "answer": "¿Hay algo en la habitación?",
    "answerarray": [
      "¿Hay",
      "algo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "habitación?"
    ],
    "options": [
      "¿Hay",
      "algo",
      "en",
      "la",
      "habitación?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a market",
    "answer": "un mercado",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "mercado"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "mercado"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a supermarket",
    "answer": "un supermercado",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "supermercado"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "supermercado"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a restaurant",
    "answer": "un restaurante",
    "answerarray": [
      "un",
      "restaurante"
    ],
    "options": [
      "un",
      "restaurante"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a supermarket near the restaurant.",
    "answer": "Hay un supermercado cerca del restaurante.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "supermercado",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "restaurante."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "un",
      "supermercado",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "restaurante."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There isn’t a market near the hotel.",
    "answer": "No hay un mercado cerca del hotel.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "un",
      "mercado",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "hay",
      "un",
      "mercado",
      "cerca",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are two supermarkets behind my house.",
    "answer": "Hay dos supermercados detrás de mi casa.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Hay",
      "dos",
      "supermercados",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "mi",
      "casa."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hay",
      "dos",
      "supermercados",
      "detrás",
      "de",
      "mi",
      "casa."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's in front of the restaurant.",
    "answer": "Está delante del restaurante.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Está",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "restaurante."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Está",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "restaurante."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't put your car in front of the market.",
    "answer": "No pongas tu coche delante del mercado.",
    "answerarray": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "tu",
      "coche",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "mercado."
    ],
    "options": [
      "No",
      "pongas",
      "tu",
      "coche",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "mercado."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Put it behind the hotel.",
    "answer": "Ponlo detrás del hotel.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Ponlo",
      "detrás",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Ponlo",
      "detrás",
      "del",
      "hotel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I think there is a cash machine in front of the bank.",
    "answer": "Pienso que hay un cajero automático delante del banco.",
    "answerarray": [
      "Pienso",
      "que",
      "hay",
      "un",
      "cajero",
      "automático",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "banco."
    ],
    "options": [
      "Pienso",
      "que",
      "hay",
      "un",
      "cajero",
      "automático",
      "delante",
      "del",
      "banco."
    ]
  }
]